Lionel Clark 657-252-7362

340 E. 1st St., Tustin, CA 92781 clarklionelfitzgerald@hotmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Over 15 years of sales experience in particularly with construction, automobiles, and storage unit industries. Stellar skills in following directions, communication, and being highly responsible. Possess an exceptional track record of reliable attendance, hardworking ethics, and a long history of team work in high stress environments.

SUMMARY OF SKILLS

- Highly motivated who is trustworthy and able to work independently.
- Strong organizational skills with the ability to creatively problem solve and execute unique projects.
- Proficient use of Microsoft Office Suite and Adobe Photoshop.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Waste Management, Orange, CA

Sorter

November 2019 to Present

- Able to sort a high volume of recyclable products in a small window.
- Capable in providing efficient work in a fast paced environment.
- Prepared to work in extreme conditions.

Convex Recyclables, San Fernando, CA

Sorting and Receiving

January 2014 to November 2016

- Ensure materials are organized and sorted properly.
- · Worked with aluminum, glass, and all plastics materials.
- Loaded all materials into puncture proof garbage bags.
- Performed minor maintenance on conveyor belt.

Urban Construction, LLC. Avrahan Vhordian, Hollywood, CA

Sales Supervisor

January 2006 to August 2011

- Supervise and monitor over 18 telemarketers.
- Responsible for any and all hiring and firings.
- · Provided dispatching and sales training for new hires.
- Highest Inhome Sales specialist for the entire team.

Best Moving Relocation, Hawaiian Gardens

Owner/Operations Supervisor

January 1999 to January 2006

- Led key projects and maintained profitability goals.
- · Planned and designed all advertising and promotional materials.
- Met with and networked with several supply vendors and mechanics.
- Set monetary goals for 2 years and hit all goals with a profit of \$770,000.

EDUCATION & TRAINING

Chrysalis, Anaheim, CA – Professional Development Certification (2019)

Watterson College, Sherman Oaks, CA – Commercial Art Certification (1995)

University of Southern California, Los Angeles, CA – Bachelor's Degree in Fine Arts (1993)